ILGWU David Dubinsky Correspondence 5780/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Collection Charges. Health, Welfare and Retirement Fund, 1954-1955 (Box 228, Folder 1a-1d)
- Collection Charges, 1954-1958 (Box 228, Folder 2a-2b)
  Schedule of Welfare Fund Collections.
- Committees, Invitations to serve on., 1951-1966 (Box 229, Folder 1a-1c)
  Arranged alphabetically by Committee or by name of recipient of award sponsored by Committee, A-B.
- Committees, Invitations to serve on. C. (Box 229, Folder 2a-2c)
- Committees, Invitations to serve on. D-F. (Box 229, Folder 3a-3b)
- Committees, Invitations to serve on. G-I. (Box 229, Folder 4)
- Committees, Invitations to serve on. J-L. (Box 230, Folder 1)
- Committees, Invitations to serve on. M-O. (Box 230, Folder 2a-2c)
- Committees, Invitations to serve on. P-R., 1960 (Box 230, Folder 3)
  Incl. letter from Eleanor Roosevelt re Puerto Rican Cultural Center.
- Committees, Invitations to serve on. S-U. (Box 230, Folder 4a-4b)
  Incl. letters from Jacob Javits, Nelson Rockefeller & Herbert Lehman re united Jewish Appeal.
- Committees, Invitations to serve on. V-Z. (Box 230, Folder 5)
- Complaints, 1966 (Box 231, Folder 1a-1c)
- Complaints, 1965 (Box 231, Folder 2a-2e)
  July-Dec. 1965.
- Complaints, 1965 (Box 232, Folder 1a-1c)
  Jan-June 1965.
- Complaints, 1964 (Box 232, Folder 2a-2d)
  July-Dec. 1964.
- Complaints, 1964 (Box 233, Folder 1a-1c)
  Jan-June 1964.
- Complaints, 1963 (Box 233, Folder 2a-2c)
  July-Dec. 1963.
- Complaints, 1963 (Box 234, Folder 1a-1d)
  Jan-June 1963.
- Complaints, 1962 (Box 234, Folder 2a-2d)
  July-Dec. 1962.
- Complaints, 1962 (Box 235, Folder 1a-1e)
  Jan-June 1962.
- Complaints, 1961 (Box 235, Folder 2a-2d)
- Complaints, 1960 (Box 236, Folder 1a-1c)
- Complaints, 1959 (Box 236, Folder 2a-2d)
- Complaints, 1958 (Box 237, Folder 1a-1d)
- Complaints, 1957 (Box 237, Folder 2a-2c)
- Congressional Record, 1956-1965 (Box 238, Folder 1)
  Letters from Congressmen & Senators w. copies of Congressional Record proceedings.
- Constitution, Union, 1932-1959 (Box 238, Folder 2)
  Incl. requests for copies; drafts of proposed constitutional changes, 1940, 1950, 1953.
- Control Department, Welfare Funds, 1962-1965 (Box 238, Folder 3)
  Arnold Bye, Wolf & Schulman, (Supervisor); incl. reports on locals.
- Control Department, 1957-1961 (Box 238, Folder 4)
- Conventions, Union, 1965 (Box 238, Folder 5a-5f)
  May 1965. Incl. comments on D.D. speech, congratulatory messages, correspondence., D.D. notes (for speech) & list of delegates.
- ILGWU, 1962 (Box 239, Folder 1)
- Delegates to 31st Convention ILGWU, 1962 (Box 239, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Correspondence, 1962 (Box 239, Folder 3)
- Election Results ILGWU, 1962 (Box 239, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Correspondence, 1959 (Box 239, Folder 5)
- ILGWU Poem, 1959 (Box 239, Folder 6)
- ILGWU Convention Delegates, 1959 (Box 239, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Convention Committees, 1959 (Box 239, Folder 8)
- ILGWU Convention Guests, 1959 (Box 239, Folder 9)
- Re: NYT, Special Supplement, 1959 (Box 239, Folder 10)
- Re: Convention Reports and Forms also for Times Supplement, 1959 (Box 239, Folder 11)
- Conventions, Union, 1956 (Box 240, Folder 1a-1e)
- Conventions, Union, 1953 (Box 240, Folder 2a-2c)
- Craft minimums, 1961-1964 (Box 241, Folder 1)
  Data on wage scales in industry.
- Credentials. Letters of introduction, A-M. (Box 241, Folder 2a-2b)
- Credentials. N-Z. (Box 241, Folder 3)
- D, 1962-1966 (Box 241, Folder 4a-4b)
- D, 1952-1961 (Box 241, Folder 4a-4b)
- Death Benefit Fund. See Union Social Insurance Programs. (Box 241, Folder 6)
- District Attorney's Office, 1949-1956 (Box 241, Folder 7a-7b)
- Drug Plan, 1960-1963 (Box 241, Folder 8)
- Misc. (Box 241A, Folder all)
- Misc., Birthday Greetings, 1942-1959 (Box 241B, Folder 1a-1b)
- Misc., Birthday Greetings, 1952 (Box 241B, Folder 2a-2c)
  60th birthday.
- Misc., Birthday Greetings, 1957 (Box 241B, Folder 3a-3b)
  65th birthday.
- Speeches and Statements, 1952 (Box 241C, Folder 1)
- S and S, 1953 (Box 241C, Folder 2)
- S and S, 1953 (Box 241C, Folder 3a-3c)
  Notes & comments on D.D.'s article, "Instead of the McCarthy Method," N.Y. Times Magazine, July 26. 1953.
- S and S, 1954 (Box 241C, Folder 4)
- S and S, 1955 (Box 241C, Folder 5)
- S and S, 1956 (Box 241C, Folder 6)
- S and S, 1957 (Box 241C, Folder 7)
- S and S, 1959 (Box 241C, Folder 8)
- S and S, 1960-1966 (Box 241C, Folder 9)
- Trip Abroad, 1953 (Box 241C, Folder 10)
  Planned trip to Israel & Sweden cancelled.
- Twenty-fifth Anniversary of D.D.'s Presidency, 1957 (Box 242, Folder 1a-1g)
  Incl. congratulatory messages; D.D. speech delivered at celebration in Madison Square Garden, June 13, 1957.
- E, 1962-1966 (Box 242, Folder 2)
  Incl. transcript of program on Wm. Green, "Never Ask What Country," presented on the Eternal Light Series for television, 1962.
- E, 1952-1961 (Box 242, Folder 3)
- Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1948-1960 (Box 242, Folder 4)
  Congratulatory message on Presidential victory & Eisenhower's reply, 1953; letter from Tracy S. Voorhees (Pres.), Comm to Study U.S. Military Assistance Program, 1959; correspondence. w. Meyer Kestenbaum on U.S. exhibition in Russia, 1959.
- F, 1962-1966 (Box 243, Folder 1a-1b)
- P, 1952-1961 (Box 243, Folder 2a-2b)
- Farmers Home Administration Loans, 1962 (Box 243, Folder 3)
  Apr-May 1962. Corres. on union investments.
- Fashion Institute of Tech., 1963-1966 (Box 243, Folder 4)
  Incl. minutes of the Educational Foundation for the Apparel Industry. Union statements in newspapers & other publications.
- FOUR, 1960-1965 (Box 243, Folder 5a-5e)
  Corres., incl. D.D. notes.
- FOUR, 1960-1963 (Box 244, Folder 1a-1c)
  Newspaper clippings files.
- FOUR, Daniels, Wilbur, 1961 (Box 244, Folder 2)
  Incl. FOUR telegram requesting recognition as collective bargaining unit; list of Union organizers.
- FOUR, 1960-1965 (Box 244, Folder 3a-3b)
  Form letters & printed material from Union.
- FOUR. General Executive Board, 1961 (Box 244, Folder 4)
  Incl. GEB statement opposing recognition of a union of business agents, Nov. 22, 1961, & correspondence.
- FOUR, 1960-1961 (Box 244, Folder 5)
  Letters from staff & Union members.
- FOUR, 1960-1961 (Box 244, Folder 6)
  Lists of Union representatives & D.D. notes.
- FOUR, 1961-1965 (Box 245, Folder 1a-1c)
  National Labor Relations Board.
- FOUR, 1961-1965 (Box 245, Folder 2)
  Newsletters.
- FOUR. Printed Matter, 1961-1965 (Box 245, Folder 3a-3b)
  Incl. declaration of principles of FOUR, and constitution.
- FOUR, 1961-1965 (Box 246, Folder 1)
  Telegrams & letters from Union field officers notifying D.D. of their withdrawal from FOUR.
- FOUR, 1961 (Box 246, Folder 2)
  Resolutions.
- FOUR. Sedares, Constantine, Chairman of FOUR, 1963-1964 (Box 246, Folder 3)
- FOUR. Socialist Party, 1961 (Box 246, Folder 4)
  Incl. Socialist Party resolution on FOUR; correspondence. w. Norman Thomas on his statement to N.Y. Herald- Tribune.
- FOUR. Staff, 1961 (Box 246, Folder 5)
  Incl. lists of officers' earnings & expenses.
- Film, "With These Hands", 1952-1959 (Box 246, Folder 6a-6b)
  Thank-you letters from institutions for use of film, requests for presentation of film.
- Film, "With These Hands", 1949-1951 (Box 246, Folder 7a-7b)
- Film, "With These Hands," Broadway premiere, 1950 (Box 246, Folder 8)
  June 15, 1950.
- Film, "With These Hands," Foreign., 1950-1957 (Box 246, Folder 9a-9b)
  Corres. on European distribution of film; incl. correspondence. on India's censoring, 1956.
- Film, "With These Hands," Printed Matter, 1950 (Box 247, Folder 1)
  Leaflets.
- Film, "With These Hands," TV Showings, 1952-1956 (Box 247, Folder 2)
- Film, "With These Hands," Washington Showing, 1952 (Box 247, Folder 3)
  March 1952.
- Fire Wardens, 1958-1964 (Box 247, Folder 4)
  Corres. w. NYC Fire Commissioners, on fire warden program.
- Africa, 1962-1963 (Box 247, Folder 5)
  Incl. American Committee on Africa.
- Africa, 1959-1961 (Box 247, Folder 6)
  Invitation to luncheon for African trade unionists, Nov. 1961; correspondence. w. Maida Springer on All- African People's Conference in Accra, Ghana, 1958; memorandum from Maida Springer on Israeli-African relations, 1959
- Australia, 1962-1965 (Box 247, Folder 7)
- Australia, 1937-1960 (Box 247, Folder 8)
  Incl. Freeland League, 1945-50.
- Austria, 1932-1966 (Box 247, Folder 9)
  I.c.w. Adolf A. Berle on the Free Austrian Legion, 1942.
- Belgium, 1938-1964 (Box 247, Folder 10)
  I.c.w. Clothing Workers Union of Belgium on transfer of membership of immigrant workers, financial assistance.
- China, 1941-1954 (Box 248, Folder 1a-1d)
  I.c.w. Chinese organizations in China & James McConaughty (President), United China Relief; plans for rehabilitation center in China, 1943-44.
- Costa Rica, 1960 (Box 248, Folder 2)
- Cuba, 1962-1966 (Box 248, Folder 3)
- Cuba, 1960-1961 (Box 248, Folder 4)
- Czechoslovakia, 1938-1958 (Box 248, Folder 5)
- Denmark, 1961 (Box 248, Folder 6)
- England, 1962-1966 (Box 248, Folder 7)
  Incl. 2 messages from Harold Wilson, thanking D.D. for congratulatory messages, 1964, 1966.
- England, 1937-1961 (Box 248, Folder 8a-8d)
  I.c.w. Hugh Gaitskell & Members of Parliament re labor problems.
- England. British Trade Union Congress, 1935-1966 (Box 249, Folder 1)
  I.c.w. Sir Walter Citrine.
- England. National Union of Tailors fie Garment Workers, 1929-1966 (Box 249, Folder 2a-2b)
- Finland, 1939-1951 (Box 249, Folder 3a-3b)
  Corres. re Finnish Relief Fund; newspaper clippings.
- France, 1940-1966 (Box 249, Folder 4a-4c)
  Incl. correspondence. re Memorial for Jewish Martyrs, 1953; correspondence. on American Aid to France.
- France. Jewish Labor Committee, 1950-1954 (Box 249, Folder 5)
  Assistance to J.L.C. for agencies, individuals & projects; incl. assistance for Unser Stimme.
- France. Le Populaire, 1948-1953 (Box 249, Folder 6)
  Incl. Leon Blum letters.
- France. Organization for Rehabilitation Through Training (ORT), 1946-1966 (Box 250, Folder 1a-1c)
- Germany, 1939-1965 (Box 250, Folder 2a-2c)
  I.c.w. Gewerkschaft Textil-Bekleidung of Germany; correspondence. re German Ladies' Garment Industry; activities of German trade unions & the role they should play in the implementation of the European Recovery Program.
- Greece, 1943-1951 (Box 250, Folder 3)
  I.c. re aid to Greece.
- Holland, 1936-1961 (Box 250, Folder 4a-4b)
- India, 1942-1958 (Box 250, Folder 5a-5b)
  I.c.w. India League of America re immigration & Indian independence, 1942-50; letters from Norman Thomas, 1951
- Israel, 1962-1966 (Box 251, Folder 1a-1b)
  Corres. on Israel; incl. letter from Ben-Gurion, July 9, 1965; Feinberg Graphics Study Room, 1966.
- Israel, 1960-1961 (Box 251, Folder 2a-2b)
  Incl. correspondence. re Joseph Breslaw Community Center; letter from Ben-Gurion, Oct. 27, 1961.
- Israel, 1951-1959 (Box 251, Folder 3a-3d)
  I.c.w. Israeli & American organizations on development of Israel.
- Israel, 1947-1950 (Box 252, Folder 1a-1c)
  Corres. re formation of the State of Israel; Union loan & related correspondence.
- Israel, 1938-1946 (Box 252, Folder 2)
  Corres. w. religious & political organizations about the formation of a Jewish state in Palestine.
- Israel. American Embassy, Tel-Aviv, 1948-1949 (Box 252, Folder 3)
  I.c.w. James McDonald (Ambassador) re Israeli situation.
- Israel. Ampal, American Israel Corp., 1959-1962 (Box 252, Folder 4)
  Financial Corres.
- Israel. Antonini Stadium, Haifa, 1959 (Box 252, Folder 5)
- Israel. Fund-raising in Industry for Israel, 1950 (Box 252, Folder 6)
  Incl. funding of the Amun-Israeli Housing Corp.
- Israel. Hebrew Univ., 1952-1966 (Box 252, Folder 7)
  I.c.w. Nelson Rockefeller & Eliahu Elath (President), Hebrew Univ.
- Israel. Histadrut, 1942-1950 (Box 253, Folder 1a-1c)
- Israel. Histadrut, N.Y., 1962-1965 (Box 253, Folder 2)
  I.c.w. Ben-Zion Ilan (American representative) on activities, especially Histadrut' s Afro-Asian Inst. in Tel-Aviv.
- Israel. Histadrut, N.Y., 1953-1960 (Box 253, Folder 3a-3b)
  Reports on Arab-Israeli situation, 1953, & related correspondence.
- Israel. Hospital at Beersheva, 1955-1965 (Box 253, Folder 4a-4c)
  Corres. on Union funding of hospital, agreement w. General Federation of Jewish Labor in Eretz Israel (Histadrut Havodim).
- Israel. ILGWU Purchases of Amun-Israeli Corporation Bonds, 1950-1951 (Box 253, Folder 5a-5b)
- Israel. ILGWU Trade School in Haifa, 1945-1957 (Box 254, Folder 1a-1b)
  I.c.w. Joseph Schlossberg, National Committee for Labor Palestine, on the Histadrut Int'l. House; Israel Merminski, American representative of Histadrut on assisting Jewish labor in Palestine, 1945-47.
- Israel. Israeli Embassy, 1948-1959 (Box 254, Folder 2a-2b)
  I.c.w. Abba Eban, Ambassador of Israel, letter from Ben-Gurion.
- Israel. Khousky, Aba, Mayor of Haifa, 1960-1964 (Box 254, Folder 3)
  Incl. correspondence. re Isidore Nagler Youth & Community Center in Haifa.
- Israel. Lieberman, Elias, 1950-1958 (Box 254, Folder 4)
  Corres. re Amun-Israeli Housing Corp.
- Israel. Mapai Printing Press, 1948-1950 (Box 254, Folder 5)
  Corres. w. Union officers & National Committee for Labor Israel on Union's donating a printing press to Mapai.
- Israel. Minutes of the Amun-Israeli Housing Corp., 1950-1955 (Box 254, Folder 6a-6b)
- Israel. State of Israel Bond Drive, 1950-1958 (Box 254, Folder 7)
  Incl. letter from Ben-Gurion, May 1951 & Abba Eban, Dec. 1950.
- Italy, 1962-1966 (Box 255, Folder 1)
  I.c.w. Giuseppe Saragat (President) on Union contribution for foundation for retarded children; correspondence. re contributions to Societa Umanitaria in Milan, 1963.
- Italy, 1952-1961 (Box 255, Folder 2a-2b)
  I.c.w. Federazione Unitaria Italiana Lavoratori Abbigliamento on labor matters & projects.
- Italy, 1949-1951 (Box 255, Folder 3a-3b)
  Incl. correspondence. on Italian labor & financial assistance.
- Italy, 1937-1948 (Box 255, Folder 4a-4b)
  Incl. correspondence. on Union contribution to the Mazzini Society.
- Italy. Carlo Tresca Home, Boys' Republic of Italy, Inc., 1949-1952 (Box 255, Folder 5)
  Incl. Antonina Cuccia (Secretary to Edward Molisani, Mgr., Local 48) report on visit to home, 1949.
- Italy. F.D. Roosevelt Institute (Palermo), 1945-1965 (Box 256, Folder 1a-1b)
- Italy. Italian-American Labor Council, 1942-1961 (Box 256, Folder 2a-2b)
  Incl. letters from Luigi Antonini (President); financial reports.
- Italy. Jewish Labor Committee, 1948-1952 (Box 256, Folder 3)
  Corres. w. ORT.
- Japan, 1962-1966 (Box 256, Folder 4)
  I.c.w. Minoru Takita (President), Japan Fed. of Textile Workers' Union.
- Japan, 1938-1961 (Box 256, Folder 5)
- Latin America, 1943-1961 (Box 256, Folder 6a-6b)
- Mexico, 1940-1965 (Box 256, Folder 7)
- Corres. arranged alphabetically by country. (Box 256, Folder 7a)
- Poland, 1937-1966 (Box 257, Folder 1a-1d)
  I.c.w. Polish Socialist Party in Great Britain, American Friends of Polish Democracy & Poland Fights, on labor matters; & with individuals on Polish situation after war re Soviet Union.
- Poland, 1948-1963 (Box 257, Folder 2a-2c)
  Letters from Relief Committee of the General Jewish Workers' Union of Poland acknowledging contributions (in Yiddish).
- Poland, 1938-1947 (Box 257, Folder 3a-3d)
  Organizations requesting funds; correspondence. w. Relief Comm. for Jewish Schools in Poland, Henryk Erlich ltr. 1938.
- Puerto Rico, 1964-1966 (Box 258, Folder 1a-1b)
  Incl. reports & newspaper clippings on minimum wage.
- Puerto Rico, 1959-1961 (Box 258, Folder 2a)
  I.c.w. Union officers, AFL-CIO, & organization in Puerto Rico re labor legislation.
- Puerto Rico, 1955-1958 (Box 258, Folder 2b)
- Puerto Rico, 1953-1954 (Box 258, Folder 3a-3c)
- Puerto Rico, 1940-1952 (Box 258, Folder 4a-4b)
- Puerto Rico. Dorvillier Newsletter. (Box 258, Folder 5)
- Rumania, 1933-1960 (Box 259, Folder 1)
  I.c.w. Rumanian Workers' Relief Comm. re financial aid.
- Russia, 1962-1965 (Box 259, Folder 2)
  I.c.w. officers of Union of Russian Jews re financial aid.
- Russia, 1948-1961 (Box 259, Folder 3a-3c)
  Incl. correspondence. re Nikita Khrushchev's visit to U.S. Sept. 1959; summary of meeting of American labor leaders & N.K., Sept. 20, 1959; correspondence. on cultural fair in Moscow 1959.
- Russia, 1938-1947 (Box 259, Folder 3d)
  Incl. correspondence., newspaper clippings on controversy between AFL & British Trade Union Congress on alliance of trade unions, correspondence. w. National Council of American & Soviet Friendship.
- Russia. Russian War Relief, Inc., 1941-1951 (Box 259, Folder 4a-4b)
- Spain, 1962-1964 (Box 260, Folder 1)
  Corres. on aid to Spanish Relief Fund Sociedades Hispanas Confederadas (Confederated Spanish Societies).
- Spain, 1938-1961 (Box 260, Folder 2a-2c)
  I.c.w. the International Solidarity Committee on aiding Spanish workers.
- Virgin Islands, 1962 (Box 260, Folder 3)
- Yugoslavia, 1950-1957 (Box 260, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Countries. Arranged alphabetically by country, A-H. (Box 260, Folder 5a-5b)
  Incl. correspondence. on the Hungarian Revolution of 1956.
- Misc. J-Z. (Box 260, Folder 6a-6c)
  Corres. on union aid to Kenya, especially the Kenya Tailors & Textile Workers Union.
- African-American Labor Center, 1964-1965 (Box 261, Folder 1)
  Letters from Irving Brown (Exec. Dir.).
- American Institute for Free Labor Development, 1963-1966 (Box 261, Folder 2a-2b)
  Incl. minutes, reports & correspondence.
- Economic Cooperation Administration, 1948-1955 (Box 261, Folder 3a-3b)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU), 1962-1965 (Box 261, Folder 4)
- ICFTU, 1954-1961 (Box 261, Folder 5)
  Incl. copies of letters & reports bet. ICFTU & AFL-CIO; letters from George Meany & ICFTU.
- ICFTU, 1949-1939 (Box 261, Folder 6a-6d)
  I.c.w. General Secretary J.H. Oldenbroek, Jay Lovestone (Exec. Secy.), Free Trade Union Comm., Wm. Green & Matthew Woll; correspondence. w. Win. Green re appointment of George Delaney as UN consultant in behalf of the ICFTU, 1951; reports, resolutions, speeches by Wm. Green, 1949; Lovestone notes; draft of constitution w. amendments received from participating countries; correspondence. on formation of ICFTU & literature.
- ICFTU. United Nations, 1948-1964 (Box 262, Folder 1)
  Incl. communiques to the governmental delegates of UN General Assembly; reports by D.D. & Matthew Woll, consultants to the UN as representatives of the AFL on the work of the Third Session to the Social Commission, April 1948.
- Int'l. Textile and Garment Workers' Federation, 1962-1966 (Box 262, Folder 2a-2b)
  Headquarters, London, England; correspondence. w. General Secretary W. J. Greenhalgh, minutes & reports.
- ITGWF, 1954-1961 (Box 262, Folder 3a-3b)
  Incl. financial correspondence. (The Int'l. Garment Workers Fed. was amalgamated w. the ITGWF in 1959.)
- ITGWF, 1948-1953 (Box 262, Folder 4a-4c)
  Corres. re affiliation, fees; minutes of Federation, 1951; correspondence. w. Charles Kreindler & Morris Bialis, delegates to meeting in Germany, 1951.
- Int'l. Transport Workers Fed., 1936-1956 (Box 262, Folder 5)
  Headquarters, London, England.
- Organizacion Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores, 1961-1965 (Box 262, Folder 6)
- F.L. A-B. (Box 263, Folder 1a-1b)
- F.L. C. (Box 263, Folder 2a-2c)
- F.L. Contributions. Arranged in reverse chronological order, 1947-1963 (Box 263, Folder 3a-3c)
- F.L. D. (Box 263, Folder 4a-4b)
- F.L. E. (Box 264, Folder 1a-1b)
- F.L. F-G. (Box 264, Folder 2a-2b)
- F.L. H-I. (Box 264, Folder 3)
- F.L. Health and Welfare. (Box 264, Folder 4)
- F.L. J-L. (Box 264, Folder 5a-5b)
- F.L. Liberal Party. (Box 264, Folder 6)
- F.L. Local Managers. (Box 264, Folder 7)
- F.L. M-N. (Box 265, Folder 1a-1c)
- F.L. O-P. (Box 265, Folder 2a-2c)
- F.L. R-S. (Box 265, Folder 3a-3c)
- F.L. Retirement Funds. (Box 266, Folder 1a-1b)
- F.L. T-Z. (Box 266, Folder 2a-2c)
- Four Freedoms Hotel, Inc., 1961-1963 (Box 266, Folder 3)
  Requests for assistance in obtaining apartments at the President Madison Hotel, Miami, Fla.
- G, 1962-1966 (Box 266, Folder 4a-4b)
  I.c.w. Harry Golden (Editor), The Carolina Israelite, on 1965 Mayoralty campaign in NYC.
- G, 1952-1961 (Box 266, Folder 5a-5b)
- The Garment Game, 1964 (Box 267, Folder 2)
  June 24, 1964. Corres. on TV program on the dress industry.
- General Executive Board, 1962-1965 (Box 267, Folder 3a-3c)
  Apr. 1962-Sept. 1965. Incl. D.D. notes, agendas, President's schedules, draft of minutes & related correspondence.
- GEB, 1959-1961 (Box 267, Folder 4a-4b)
  Aug. 1959-June 1961.
- GEB, 1957-1959 (Box 267, Folder 5a-5b)
  Jan. 1957-Apr. 1959.
- GEB, 1952-1956 (Box 268, Folder 1a-1d)
  Mar. 1952-Apr. 1956.
- GEB. Decisions, A-C. (Box 268, Folder 2a-2c)
  Arranged alphabetically by decision; incl. index to decisions; correspondence. & decisions prior to 1951.
- GEB. Decisions, C. Conventions. (Box 268, Folder 3a-3d)
  Decisions on postponement of Union conventions; 1942 convention to May 1944 by referendum; postponement of 1939 convention to May 1940; convention of 1936 postponed to May 1937.
- GEB. Dec., D-F. (Box 269, Folder 1a-1b)
- GEB. Dec., G-K. (Box 269, Folder 2a-2b)
- GEB. Dec., L-N. (Box 269, Folder 3a-3c)
- GEB. Dec., O-P. (Box 269, Folder 4)
- GEB. Dec., R-S. (Box 269, Folder 5a-5b)
- GEB. Dec., T-Z. Incl. inquiries re United Front. (Box 270, Folder 1a-1c)
- GEB. Hearing, 1949 (Box 270, Folder 2a-2d)
  Charges brought by a group of members against the Los Angeles Cloak & Dress Jt. Bds., officers & members of each of the Executive Boards of Locals 65, 84, 96, & 97; incl. petition, telegrams, letters from local members affiliated w. Cloak Jt. Bd., minutes of hearing, March, by special GEB committee, Luigi Antonini (Chairman); GEB decision.
- GEB. Merger of Local Unions, 1959-1960 (Box 271, Folder 1)
  Incl. letters from Union officers presenting their position on merging locals, GEB decision 1963.
- GEB. N.Y. Board Meetings, 1938-1966 (Box 271, Folder 2)
  Notices.
- GEB. N.Y. Local Managers' Meetings, 1964-1966 (Box 271, Folder 3)
  Notices; incl. report of Jan. 24, 1964 meeting.
- Gerechtiqkeit, 1958 (Box 271, Folder 4a-4b)
  Corres. on decision to cease publication of Gerechtigkeit, Jan. 1958. Correspondents incl. officers, members, outside organizations, & last issue.
- Grand Jury Trucking Investigation, 1959 (Box 271, Folder 5)
  June 26, 1959. Subpoena (copy) to Merchants Ladies' Garment Association.
- Green, William, 1951 (Box 271, Folder 6)
  Oct. 1951. Publ. A Tribute to Wm. Green by the Jewish Labor Committee.
- Guaranteed Annual Wage. (Box 271, Folder 7)
- H, 1962-1966 (Box 271, Folder 8)
- Harriman, Averell, 1954-1959 (Box 271, Folder 9)
  I.c.w. Governor's office on Workmen's Compensation & Moreland Commission. (12 letters)
- Health and Welfare Funds. See ILGWU Social Insurance Programs. (Box 271, Folder 10)
- Hirsch, Ben B. (Barney), 1948-1955 (Box 271, Folder 11)
- Impartial Chairmen (I.C.), 1941 (Box 272, Folder 1)
  Children's Dress.
- I.C. Los Angeles and San Francisco Dress Industry, 1942-1952 (Box 272, Folder 2)
  I.c.w. Anthony G. O'Rourke (I.C.) on wage stabilization fie job classification.
- I.C. N.Y. Coat and Suit Industry, 1963 (Box 272, Folder 3)
- I.C. N.Y. Coat and Suit Industry, 1935-1950 (Box 272, Folder 4)
  Incl. decisions of Sol Rosenblatt & James J. Walker; correspondence. re cases, schedule of hearings; Sol Rosenblatt address before AFL conventions, 1935 & 1938.
- I.C. N.Y. Corset and Brassiere Industry, 1938-1944 (Box 272, Folder 5)
  Corres. w. Maxwell Copelof; decisions.
- I.C. N.Y. Dress Ind., 1936-1959 (Box 272, Folder 6)
  Corres. w. Harry Uviller (I.c.); decisions.
- I.C. N.Y. Knitgoods Ind., 1935-1936 (Box 272, Folder 7)
  Decisions of Tracy S. Voorhees (I.c.).
- I.C. N.Y. Shoulder Pads Ind. (Women's Apparel), 1950 (Box 272, Folder 8)
  Decision of I.c. Nathan Wolf, March.
- I.C. N.Y. Snowsuits Ind., 1959 (Box 272, Folder 9)
  Decision of George Mintzer (I.c.), Aug.
- Union Depts., 1958-1965 (Box 273, Folder 1)